fcgov.com 2009-12-17

# Legal notices, disclaimer, accessibility statement: City of Fort Collins

City of Fort Collins retains copyrights on all text, graphic images, design, sound, and other content. This means that you may not: distribute the text or graphics to others without the express permission of the City of Fort Collins; "mirror" this information on your server without our permission; or modify or re-use the text or graphics on this system. You may print copies of the information for your own personal use and; reference this server from your own documents. Commercial use of the materials is prohibited without the permission of the City of Fort Collins. In all copies of this information, you must retain this notice and any other copyright notices originally included with such information. 

The City of Fort Collins reserves all other rights. 

Copyright © 1996-2009, City of Fort Collins 

The City of Fort Collins maintains this web site to enhance public access to City information. This is a service that is continually under development, and despite efforts to keep the information timely and accurate, users should be aware that the information available on this Web site may not be timely, accurate or complete, and may not reflect official positions of the City. Please feel free to notify the webmaster of any errors that come to your attention as you use this Web site. 

Reference herein to any specific commercial products, process, or service by trade name, trademark, manufacturer, or otherwise, does not constitute or imply endorsement or, recommendation of the same, by or favoring by the City of Fort Collins. 

The documents on this web site contain hypertext pointers (or "links") to information created and maintained by other public and private organizations. Please be aware that we the City of Fort Collins does not control or guarantee the accuracy, relevance, timeliness, or completeness of this outside information. Further, the inclusion of pointers to particular items in hypertext is not intended to reflect their importance, nor is it intended to endorse any views expressed or products or services offered by the author of the reference or the organization operating the server on which the reference is maintained. 

The City of Fort Collins is committed to protecting online users' privacy. Protection of personal privacy on the Internet promotes citizen confidence, increases participation in online activities and supports effective delivery of services. The purpose of our policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather when you visit our site, how we may use that information, and whether we disclose it to anyone. 

**Information collected for statistical purposes**  
We automatically collect electronically generated information about your visit to our site, such as the date, type of browser used, and technical Internet protocol data. We collect this information about each user session from our user logs, and refer to it in summary form for identifying trends. Our goal in using this type of information is to help us make our site more useful to visitors, to learn about the number of visitors and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record information about individuals and their visits. 

**How we collect and use personal information**  
If you submit a question or comment that contains personally identifying information, we will only use the personally identifiable information to respond to your request and analyze trends. If necessary, we may redirect your message to another government agency or person who is in a better position to answer your question.  
If you subscribe to any of our online subscriptions, your email address is used only to deliver the subscription you opted into. We do not compile information on subscriptions, historical or otherwise, and you have the option to stop future mailings at any time. 

**Control of personal information**  
At any time while accessing our site, any user may decline participation in any activity that asks for information (i.e. survey, e-mail or e-commerce). Your choice not to participate will in no way affect your ability to use any other feature on our site. In online applications that ask for personal information, you have the option of canceling and terminating the application. You also are provided a way to "unsubscribe" to any newsletters, notices, schedules, etc., sent to you by email in our various contact services (listservs). 

**How we protect your personal information**  
We use industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, including encryption using secure sockets layer (SSL). We will take all reasonable precautions to safeguard the confidentiality of such information, but shall nevertheless NOT be held liable for any injury caused by the disclosure of that information, whether caused by security breach, accident, inadvertence, or any other act resulting in disclosure. 

**What we provide to third parties**  
As a governmental agency, we are governed by public records laws. Any information that we receive through use of our site is subject to the same provisions as information provided on paper. We do not share personal identifying information with any third party without your permission. We disclose only in aggregate form our statistical analyses or demographics of users to third parties. This information is not reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information, and will not be released to any outside parties unless we are legally required to do so in connection with law enforcement investigations or other legal proceedings. 

**How we use "cookies"**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that browsers store on your computer. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis. We do not store any personal information in cookies. Even if you do not use cookies, you can still access all of the features on our site. 

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**Tell us what you think**  
We at the City of Fort Collins welcome your questions and comments about our privacy policy. Please send e-mail to [webmaster@fcgov.com](mailto:webmaster@fcgov.com)
